

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

# **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and magni dolores eos qui ratione voluptatem sequi nesciunt. Neque porro quisquam est, qui dolo of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

# **EDUCATION**



### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. t..." Translation by H. Rackham: "On the other hand, administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

# **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

## **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult i, id est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expedita distinctio. and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

# **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to 45 trước Công Nguyên, nghĩa là nó đã có khoảng hơ goods in and out

- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

**Recognition and Gains:** 

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# ACTIVITIES



Sep 2003 - 2007

### **CVPRO JSC**

### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer pport. Dona' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US word choi

# **REFERENCES**



### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

## **SKILLS**





# **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt d when nothing prevents our being able to d and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities